guildwars2forum.com 2009-12-16

# iEntry Network - Privacy Policy

iEntry reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users through a notice posted on iEntry.com or by email, of the existence of a new privacy policy or any updates. 

**Registration**  
iEntry collects personally identifying information only during the registration process. Information is collected in certain portions of iEntry in which users specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, jayde.com submissions or suggestions. iEntry may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, editorial and feedback purposes. Information submitted at the time of registration (including newsletter subscriptions) may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by iEntry and may be shared with companies that have something of value to offer. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use -- either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online. **

Cookies

**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major Web sites.

Cookies help make iEntry better, by showing how and when guests use the site. Many content improvements and updates are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. A cookie lets iEntry remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information although it may enable iEntry to relate a user's use of iEntry to personally identifying information that has previously been submitted by the user, if any. 

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. These cookies are sent from third-party computers and are subject to such third parties' policies. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, it is likely that most areas of the site will not function properly if you do so. **

Removal from our Database

**  
Should you ever wish to be removed from our database, simply contact us and we will be happy to fulfill your request. Additionally, should you wish further clarification of this policy, please do not hesitate to email us at **[support@ientry.com](mailto:support@ientry.com)**.
